edmtrain.com 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy | edmtrain

Thanks for using edmtrain!

Privacy Policy.

By using this application, services, or website ("Application"), you are agreeing to the policy here. If you do not agree to the policy below, please do not access or use the Application. This policy may be modified at any time, and the latest version will be posted here. Use of the Application shall constitute your agreement to any changes to the Privacy Policy.

Information We Collect.

1\. This Application uses Google Analytics for determining statistics such as how many people are using the Application, what kinds of devices are being used, what events are popular, and what locations are popular. Google Analytics does not provide us with any personally identifiable information.

2\. This Application links to third parties that may provide us with statistics such as number of referrals.

3\. When subscribing to notifications, we will use your email address to send you notifications about events. We do not share your email address with any third parties, and you can unsubscribe at any time.

4\. This Application uses Google's Map API for searching venue addresses. View [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy).

5\. If you have an account, we use your Facebook user id for signing in. We do not share your Facebook user id with other third parties.

6\. If you have an account, we save data from activities you perform, such as your user profile and history of submitted events. Personally identifiable information associated with your account is not shared with any third parties.

7\. We collect error information, which contains information about the user agent and nothing personally identifiable.

8\. To display locations near you, we may use an IP geolocation service to estimate your state/province.

Information We Share.

We may share aggregate information such as how many people viewed an event, or how many clicked a link to a particular venue.

If you have an account, the information you submit may be displayed publicly, such as your chosen username next to an event that you added. We do not share any personally identifiable information with any third parties.

Third Parties.

This Application contains links to third party websites, as well as references to names, content, products or services provided by third parties. By including these links and references, EDM Train LLC does not represent these parties, their content or any products and services they offer. You are responsible for knowing when you are visiting a third party website, and for knowing the terms of use and privacy policy for each such third party website.

Ticket websites, guestlists, reduced admission, and hotels are a few examples of such third party websites.
